[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is Drug Addiction?",
    "options": [
      "Addiction to Food",
      "Dependence on Drugs",
      "Taking medicines with valid medical prescriptions",
      "Not eating a balanced diet"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "In which age group, Drug addiction is a major problem?",
    "options": ["Childhood", "Adolescence", "Adulthood", "Old Age"],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "When is International Day Against Drug Abuse celebrated?",
    "options": ["26th June", "12th August", "14th September", "1st December"],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a symptom of mental illness?",
    "options": [
      "Insomnia",
      "Depression",
      "Positive attitude",
      "Delusions and hallucinations"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Legally Drug Abuse is the intake of drugs with valid medical prescriptions and for Medical purposes.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following was a major reason for the development of Drugs?",
    "options": [
      "For clinical purposes",
      "To experience hallucinations",
      "Adventure",
      "For curiosity"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a common reason for Drug Abuse or Drug Dependence?",
    "options": [
      "Peer Pressure",
      "Adventure",
      "A feeling of Excitement and Euphoria",
      "For death"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Alcohol abuse is greatest among which of these age groups?",
    "options": [
      "15- to 17-year-olds",
      "18- to 29-year-olds",
      "30- to 54-year-olds",
      "55 and older"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Alcohol-use disorder increases your risk for:",
    "options": ["Cancer", "Pancreatitis", "Liver damage"],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which of the following is an important factor in substance abuse?",
    "options": [
      "Whether the substances are regularly used by other family members",
      "Whether the family environment is rural or urban",
      "Whether you are a twin",
      "Whether you are born in the winter"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  }
]